RG 062:080, Town of Meriden
Connecticut State Library
Town of Meriden records
1806-1926
Connecticut State Library
Meriden (Conn.)
35 cubic feet
Administrative and tax records for the town of Meriden.
RG062_080
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Meriden was incorporated in May 1806 and was taken from Wallingford. The city was incorporated in May 1867. The town and city consolidated on January 1, 1922.
Scope and Content
Administrative and tax records for the town of Meriden.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Meriden -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Meriden -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Meriden -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Meriden -- Registers
Places:
Meriden (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1806-1926
  - T000266
    - Town and city tax collectors' lists, 1879-1926 (Box Boxes 1-2)
    - Tax abatement record, 1832-1861 (Box Box 3)
    - Collector's blotter, 1893-1895 (Box Box 3)
    - Treasurer's collection list, 1893-1895 (Box Box 3)
    - Record of expenditures, 1806-1857 (Box Box 3)
    - Selectmen's list of orders and relief correspondence, 1875-1878 (Box Box 3)
    - Cancelled checks and withdrawal requests, 1861-1873 (Box Box 4)
  - 1986-006
    - Rate bill books
      - 1893, 1 volume
      - 1894, 2 volumes
      - 1895, 2 volumes
      - 1897, 2 volumes
      - 1898, 2 volumes
    - Tax abstracts (Grand lists), 1822-1912; 151 volumes
      - 1822, 1824, 1825, 1827, 1828, 1829, 1830, 1831, 1832, 1833, 1834, 1836, 1837 (Box Box 1)
      - 1838, 1839, 1840, 1841, 1842, 1843, 1844, 1845, 1846 (Box Box 2)
      - 1847, 1848, 1849, 1850, 1851 (Box Box 3)
      - Corner School District, 1851 (Box Box 3)
      - 1852, 1853, 1854, 1855, 1856, 1857, 1858, 1859 (Box Box 4)
      - 1860, 1861, 1862, 1863, 1864 (Box Box 5)
      - 1865, 1866 (Box Box 6)
      - Town of Meriden, 1867 (Box Box 6)
      - City of Meriden, 1867 (Box Box 6)
      - Town of Meriden, 1868 (Box Box 7)
      - City of Meriden, 1868 (Box Box 7)
      - Town of Meriden, 1869 (Box Box 7)
      - Town of Meriden, 1870 (Box Box 8)
      - City of Meriden, 1870 (Box Box 8)
      - Town of Meriden, 1871 (Box Box 8)
      - City of Meriden, 1871 (Box Box 8)
      - Town of Meriden, 1872 (Box Box 9)
      - City of Meriden, 1872 (Box Box 9)
      - Town of Meriden, 1873 (Box Box 9)
      - City of Meriden, 1873 (Box Box 9)
      - City of Meriden, 1873 (Box Box 9)
      - Town of Meriden, 1874 (Box Box 10)
      - City of Meriden, 1874 (Box Box 10)
      - Corner School District, 1874 (Box Box 10)
      - Center School District, 1874 (Box Box 10)
      - Town of Meriden, 1875 (Box Box 11)
      - Corner School District, 1875 (Box Box 11)
      - Town of Meriden, 1876 (Box Box 11)
      - City of Meriden, 1876; 2 volumes (Box Box 11)
      - Town of Meriden, 1877 (Box Box 12)
      - City of Meriden, 1877-1878 (Box Box 12)
      - Town of Meriden, 1878 (Box Box 12)
      - Corner School District, 1878 (Box Box 12)
      - West School District, 1878; 2 volumes (Box Box 13)
      - Town of Meriden, 1879 (Box Box 13)
      - City of Meriden, 1879 (Box Box 13)
      - Center School District, 1879 (Box Box 13)
      - Town of Meriden, 1880 (Box Box 14)
      - City of Meriden, 1880 (Box Box 14)
      - Center School District, 1880 (Box Box 14)
      - Prattsville School District, 1880 (Box Box 14)
      - Town of Meriden, 1881 (Box Box 15)
      - City of Meriden, 1881 (Box Box 15)
      - Corner School District, 1881 (Box Box 15)
      - West School District, 1881 (Box Box 15)
      - Town of Meriden, 1882 (Box Box 16)
      - City of Meriden, 1882-1883 (Box Box 16)
      - Town of Meriden, 1883 (Box Box 16)
      - West School District, 1883, 1884, 1885; 1 volume (Box Box 16)
      - Center School District, 1883, 1884, 1885, 1886; 1 volume (Box Box 17)
      - Town of Meriden, 1884 (Box Box 17)
      - City of Meriden, 1884 (Box Box 17)
      - Corner School District, 1884 (Box Box 17)
      - Town of Meriden, 1885 (Box Box 18)
      - City of Meriden, 1885 (Box Box 18)
      - Town of Meriden, 1886 (Box Box 19)
      - City of Meriden, 1886 (Box Box 19)
      - Corner School District, 1886 (Box Box 19)
      - West School District, 1886 (Box Box 19)
      - Town of Meriden, 1887 (Box Box 20)
      - City of Meriden, 1887 (Box Box 20)
      - Corner School District, 1887 (Box Box 20)
      - Town of Meriden, 1888 (Box Box 21)
      - City of Meriden, 1888 (Box Box 21)
      - Railroad District, 1888 (Box Box 21)
      - Town of Meriden, 1889 (Box Box 22)
      - City of Meriden, 1889 (Box Box 22)
      - Town of Meriden, 1890 (Box Box 23)
      - City of Meriden, 1890 (Box Box 23)
      - Center School District, 1890 (Box Box 23)
      - Town of Meriden, 1891 (Box Box 23)
      - City of Meriden, 1891 (Box Box 23)
      - Town of Meriden, 1892 (Box Box 24)
      - City of Meriden, 1892 (Box Box 24)
      - Corner School District, 1892 (Box Box 24)
      - West School District, 1892 (Box Box 24)
      - Town of Meriden, 1893 (Box Box 25)
      - City of Meriden, 1893 (Box Box 25)
      - Town of Meriden, 1894 (Box Box 25)
      - City of Meriden, 1894 (Box Box 25)
      - Town of Meriden, 1895 (Box Box 26)
      - City of Meriden, 1895 (Box Box 26)
      - City of Meriden, 1896 (Box Box 26)
      - Town of Meriden, 1896; 1 volume
        This volume is not boxed and is on oversize shelving.
      - Town of Meriden, 1897 (Box Box 27)
      - City of Meriden, 1897 (Box Box 27)
      - Town of Meriden, 1898 (Box Box 27)
      - City of Meriden, 1898 (Box Box 27)
      - Town of Meriden, 1899 (Box Box 28)
      - City of Meriden, 1899 (Box Box 28)
      - Town of Meriden, 1900 (Box Box 29)
      - City of Meriden, 1900 (Box Box 29)
      - Town of Meriden, 1901 (Box Box 29)
      - City of Meriden, 1901 (Box Box 29)
      - Town of Meriden, 1902 (Box Box 30)
      - City of Meriden, 1902 (Box Box 30)
      - Town of Meriden, 1903 (Box Box 30)
      - City of Meriden, 1903 (Box Box 30)
      - City of Meriden, 1904 (Box Box 31)
      - Town of Meriden, 1904 (Box Box 31)
      - City of Meriden, 1905 (Box Box 32)
      - Town of Meriden, 1905 (Box Box 32)
      - City of Meriden, 1906 (Box Box 33)
      - Town of Meriden, 1906 (Box Box 33)
      - City of Meriden, 1907 (Box Box 34)
      - Town of Meriden, 1907 (Box Box 34)
      - City of Meriden, 1908 (Box Box 35)
      - Town of Meriden, 1908 (Box Box 35)
      - City of Meriden, 1909 (Box Box 36)
      - Town of Meriden, 1909 (Box Box 36)
      - City of Meriden, 1910 (Box Box 37)
      - Town of Meriden, 1910 (Box Box 37)
      - Town of Meriden, 1911 (Box Box 38)
      - City of Meriden, 1911 (Box Box 38)
      - Town of Meriden, 1912 (Box Box 39)
      - City of Meriden, 1912 (Box Box 39)